So here's what you missed on Glee.Sue framed Figgins so she could take his job
歡樂合唱團前情提要 Sue誣陷Figgins 搶了他的工作
- so now she's principal and Becky's her Beckretary.- Get out,bitch!
- 現在她是校長 Becky是小B秘書 - 滾啦 賤人
Kurt started a cover band  called Pamela Lansbury and Rachel's in it
Kurt搞了個翻唱樂隊 名曰Pamela Lansburyand 喊上了Rachel
and so is Santana and so is Dani and so is Elliot,
Santana和Dani 還有Elliot
- who they also call Star Child but his name's really Elliot.- Oh,my God,Star Child.
- 他人稱星之子 不過真名叫Elliot - 神呀 星之子
Jake used to be a man-slut but then he wasn't  because he met Marley
Jake以前可花心 遇到Marley後變了
but then he cheated on Marley with Bree  which was so super mean
可又背著Marley和Bree搞上 真不像話
because Marley's so nice and Bree's so horrible and it's like,geez,
因為Marley是好姑娘 Bree可壞了 我看是...
I guess he's a man-slut again.That's so sad.
又變回花心男了 真可惜
My Aunt Felicia always says,"A tiger can't change his stripes.
我姨Felicia總說 本性難移
And that's what you missed on Glee.
就是這些啦
Hey,um,guys!Guys... New Directions!New Directions!Guys!
小夥伴們 合唱團 各位
Hey!I just ran into Mr.Shue,and he's gonna be stuck  in his classroom for the rest of the afternoon
我剛碰到鞋老師 他下午在教室 來不了
because of some school board inspection thing,but he still wanted us to meet
因為校董會有檢查 他說我們還是該碰頭
- so we can start working on ideas for nationals.- Beyonc!
- 想想全國賽唱什麼 - 碧昂絲
This is anarchy!We can't... we can't all just shout at the same time.
太亂啦 不能一起嚷啊
That's better.I have some ideas already.
這才對 我有點想法
I'm thinking  that the music needs to be really simple,so we can really highlight our voices.
音樂要簡單些 才好突出歌聲
No guitars,or nothing electronic.We go with a simple piano arrangement.Which I could play.
不用吉他 電子樂 我彈鋼琴就好
- I'm assuming you're singing lead?- Well,I am a senior,and this is my last go at it.
- 主唱也是你唄 - 我高三了 最後一次嘛
We need to win this.
我們一定要贏
- Well,feels like North Korea up in here.- Okay,forget the piano.Forget all the music.
- 北朝鮮耶 - 好吧 鋼琴和音樂都算了
We could just do,um,a cappella,that always works.
那就清唱聖歌 這總可以
Warblers.Should we wear matching blazers,too?
成鳴鳥了 是不是還要穿你們的校服啊
Let's take it back... What was wrong with the guitars?
話說回來 吉他有什麼不好
Nothing,why can't you guys just stop resisting me  for a second,and just go with me?
沒有 你們別搗亂啦 聽我的行嗎
- Okay,Blaine Jong-il.- Yes!Blaine Jong-il
- Blaine是金胖子
I am not trying to be bossy.I am trying to give the benefit of my experience.
我不是專制 只是想用經驗幫助大家
I have won more show choir competitions than anyone in this room.
我得的獎比你們都多吧
You suck.
你好極品
- A capella is worth a shot.Let's do it.- Thank you.
- 清唱聖歌 值得一試 - 謝謝支持
- Then you two can have fun in your little barbershop couplet  while the rest of us discuss something good.- Fine.
- 那你倆私聊吧 我們要找好歌呢 - 夠了
You don't want my help...  ...then I am not gonna give it.
你們不要我幫助 那我不幫了
- Looks like somebody's man-struating.- I heard that.
- 這小哥來大姨媽了吧 - 我聽見了
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸園美劇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-橙子
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: 南極洲洲長 風聲 Solitary 琥珀時間 校對: Andrea∞Quinn 時間軸:YTET-橙子
Glee Season5Episode 7
歡樂合唱團 第五季 第七集
Oh,good.We're all here.
真好 都到了
Thank you,Team Pamela Lansbury,for assembling on such short notice.
謝謝Pamela Lansbury樂隊的及時到來
Okay,well,I rescheduled my dialect session,so what's up with this emergency text?
我可是調了方言課 什麼事這麼急
- What's up is I just booked our band's debut gig!- Amazing.Where?When?
- 事情就是 樂隊就要首演啦 - 太好了 何時何地
This Thursday,7:30 p.m.,at the Greenwich Village hot-spot Callbacks.
週四晚七點半 格林威治村 "複試"酒吧
Ooh,NYADA's premier piano bar.
哇 NYADA第一鋼琴吧
Hold on,isn't that a Broadway hangout?
等等 那裡都是音樂劇粉絲
Well,traditionally,but I talked to the manager,and he says that Thursdays are kind of their dead nights.
一般來說是的 但我問了經理 他說週四生意比較差
So we can go in and do whatever we want.
我們愛唱什麼唱什麼
No way,we cannot debut there.That is instant career suicide.
不行 在那裡首演 以後就不用混了
Yeah,Kurt,look,not to overstep,
是啊 Kurt 我不想越權
but I-I follow a lot of bands just starting out,and it's kind of all about the launch.
我參加過不少新樂隊 首演真的很關鍵
You know,getting music critics out to see you,and that's a lot easier with the right venue.
要想樂評家注意到 得找對地方才行
Oh,come on,Callbacks is a real funky place.You know,they've got tons of history.
別這樣 "複試"還挺潮的 有不少歷史
Yeah,but I can't think  of a single band that started out there.
但沒有樂隊在那裡發家
I mean,it's not like The Bitter End or the Mercury Lounge,or...
不能和The Bitter End Mercury Lounge這些音樂夜店比
Yeah,and if people associate that place  with show tunes,nobody's gonna come out for...
如果那裡都是音樂劇粉 誰又會來看...
Our covers of Madonna's greatest hits?I disagree,Dani.
我們翻唱麥當娜嗎 我不同意 Dani
- Oh,so we're back to the whole Madonna thing?- Yes,it was my first impulse.
- 又是麥當娜嗎 - 這是我的第一感覺
Okay,look,guys,I know it's untraditional,but you have to trust me.
小夥伴們 我知道這有點另類 但你們要相信我
I was there at Callbacks.I saw it all,a vision of perfect clarity.Every seat was occupied.
我在那裡 好像清楚地看到了 我們的表現 全場爆滿
A quiet hush fell over the expectant crowd.As Pamela Lansbury made their way to the stage,
人們屏息凝神 充滿期待 樂隊走上舞台
and the opening notes of Madonna's 1985 single hit "Into the Groove" begin.
開唱麥當娜85年單曲"Into the Groove"
*And you can dance *
And you can dance
*For inspiration *
For inspiration
*Get into the groove,boy *
Get into the groove,boy
*You've got to prove your love to me *
You've got to prove your love to me
*Yeah *Get up on your feet,yeah,step to the beat *
Yeah, Get up on your feet,yeah,step to the beat
*Boy,what will it be *Music can be such a revelation *
Boy,what will it be Music can be such a revelation
*Dancing around you feel the sweet sensation *
Dancing around you feel the sweet sensation
*We might be lovers if the rhythm's right *
We might be lovers if the rhythm's right
*I hope this feeling never ends tonight *
I hope this feeling never ends tonight
*Only when I'm dancing can I feel this free *
Only when I'm dancing can I feel this free
*At night I lock the doors where no one else can see *
At night I lock the doors where no one else can see
*I'm tired of dancing here all by myself *
I'm tired of dancing here all by myself
*Tonight I want to dance with someone else *
Tonight I want to dance with someone else
*Get into the groove,boy *You've got to prove your love to me *
Get into the groove,boy You've got to prove your love to me
*Yeah,get up on your feet *
Yeah,get up on your feet
*Yeah,step to the beat *
Yeah,step to the beat
*Boy,what can it be,yeah *Live out your fantasy here with me *
Boy,what can it be,yeah Live out your fantasy here with me
*Just let the music set you free *
Just let the music set you free
*Touch my body,move in time *  *Now I know you're mine *
Touch my body,move in time Now I know you're mine
*Now I know you're mine *You've got to get into the groove,boy *
You've got to get into the groove,boy
*You've got to prove your love to me *
You've got to prove your love to me
*Yeah,get up on your feet *Yeah,step to the beat *Boy,what will it be *
Yeah,get up on your feet Yeah,step to the beat Boy,what will it be
*You have to get into the groove *
You have to get into the groove
*Boy,you got to prove your love to me *
Boy,you got to prove your love to me
*Get up on your feet *Yeah,step to the beat *Boy,what will it be *
Get up on your feet Yeah,step to the beat Boy,what will it be
*You've got to get into the groove.*
You've got to get into the groove.
Oh,it's my fianc.Talk amongst yourselves.Hello?
是我未婚夫 你們先聊 喂
Oh,can I just say Glee Club sucks!Mr.Shue asked for ideas for nationals.
我能說合唱團很討厭嗎 鞋老師讓討論全國賽的歌
And when I gave some genius ones,everyone got all mad and started dissing me.
我的主意很棒 但大家都很不爽 還攻擊我
Maybe I came on too strong.But since when is that a bad thing?
也許我有點強勢 但強勢有什麼不好
It's not,but you got to remember,at McKinley everyone has an equal vote.
不是不好 但要記住 在麥金利 人人都有話語權
And if you come on too aggressively,they might think you're a control-freak or a puppet master.
如果你太著急 別人會覺得你控制欲強 總想指揮大家
Anyway... I was gonna call you.Pamela Lansbury booked its first gig.
我正想找你呢 Pamela Lansbury定下了首演計劃
And I know you were just here,but I was hoping you could come cheer us on in the audience.
我知道你剛來過 不過 很希望你來給我們加油呢
So,what do you say... can I send you the deets?And a JetBlue voucher?
怎麼樣 給你發去 時間地點吧 還有廉價機票
Uh,of course,I wouldn't miss it.Wow,I can't believe anyone would see me as controlling.
當然 我不會錯過 怎麼會有人覺得我控制欲強呢
- You missed a spot.- I'm doing the best I can,Sue.
- 漏了那點 - 我盡力了 Sue
You know,the way you clean these floors  is a perfect metaphor for the way you ran this school.
你擦地擦得差 當校長也一樣
You did your best,but your best just wasn't good enough.
你盡力了 但就是不夠好
Look,I know you're upset  that the school board is coming today to evaluate McKinley,
我知道你很不爽 因為校董會要來評估學校
and to determine if I'm worthy to be instated as full-time principal.
決定是否任命我為全職校長
And do you realize in my short time as acting principal,test scores have risen 42%.
你發現了嗎 我當代理校長短短幾個月 考試成績提高了42%
And my new caning policy has dropped both absences and tardiness down to zero.
鞭笞政策也消滅了曠課和拖拉現象
So,the truth is you should be cleaning floors and I should be running schools.
所以說你擦地板 我當校長 是合理的
And if you would like to continue cleaning floors  and feeding your family,
如果你還想繼續擦地 養家餬口
I suggest you do  everything you can to make sure this place looks just amazing  for this evaluation.
我建議你 評估期間 好好努力 把學校弄乾淨些
They're in your office,Coach.
他們在您辦公室啦 教練
One last question before we come back  for the official evaluation later in the week.
先問最後一個問題 稍後再來正式評估
Why do you want to be a principal?
你為什麼想當校長
Now,I know everyone wants to wear the crown,but the fantasy of it  can be quite different from the reality.
我知道 大家都愛這個光環 但理想與現實總有些不同
Well,more than anyone I have ever met,I was born to be in charge.
我和別人不一樣 生來就是領導者
Test scores are up.Kids are showing up.Our sports teams are winning.
考試成績好了 學生缺勤少了 校隊贏得比賽
Heck,even the Glee Club is back competing  for the national title of clubs no one really cares about.
連合唱團也在參加沒人看的全國賽
And all of this is happening because I can finally manifest my vision  without having to clear it with some fool.
這都是因為 我落實治校願景 不用再向某個蠢貨請示
You give me this school,and in one year  it will be the top school in the state.I guarantee it.
把學校交給我 我保證 再過一年 它會成為全州最好的
I'm a champion,gentlemen.Let me be your champion.
我是贏家 先生們 讓我成為你們的贏家
We'll be back in a week.
我們一周後再來
But between you and me,barring a total catastrophe,you have my vote.
但私下說句 除非天塌下來 我一定投你
You certainly have a lot of trophies,Principal Sylvester.
你獲得過很多榮譽 Sylvester校長
Well,Superintendent Harris,you're new in town,you may not be aware,
Harris老闆 你剛來 可能還不清楚
but I am the only seven-time national champion cheerleading coach  in the country.
我帶拉拉隊拿過7次全國冠軍 是全國僅有的
- Hmm,my wife used to watch those competitions on television.- Mm-hmm.
我太太常看拉拉隊比賽
Bugged the crap out of me if I'm gonna be totally honest.
說來傷心
- We're divorced.Are you married?- No,no.I married myself once,but I don't think it was legal.
- 我們離婚了 你結婚了嗎 - 沒有 我和自己結過 估計州里不認
We should go out for a beer sometime.
我們該一起喝點啤酒
Oh,are you sure that's appropriate,Bob?
這合適嗎 Bob
I don't think anyone would see a couple of guys going out  for a beer as anything shady.
哥幾個喝點啤酒 很正常啦
Besides I'm new in town.I'd like to find some great dudes to hang out with.
何況 我剛來這裡 很希望有哥們一起玩
I-I'll call your office,okay?
我再打你辦公室電話 行嗎
I'm lactose intolerant,and I may have to fart,Coach.
我乳糖不耐 好像要放屁 教練
I don't look masculine,do I,Becky?
我像個哥嗎 Becky
- You have an allure that goes beyond gender.- That's what I always say.
- 你的魅力超越了性別 - 我一直是這麼說
I have to admit,while I find his hairline highly suspicious for a man his age,
不過要承認 我覺得 以他這把年紀 那頭髮一定是假的
that Bob Harris thinks I could star in the sequel to Boys Don't Cry,honestly,it kind of bums me out.
Bob Harris認為我可以出演男孩別哭續集 說實話 這有點惹惱我了
Maybe it's your clothes.You could try on a skirt every now and then.
可能是你穿衣風格的問題 你可以時不時地試一下短裙呀
No,you don't understand the era I grew up in.I became a teacher almost 30 years ago.It was 1986.
不是 你不瞭解我成長的時代 我差不多30年前開始做老師 那是1986年
It was a different time.
時代大不同
I tried being girly.But I found it hard to get the respect I felt I deserved.
我試著女性化一些 但我發現很難得到應有的尊重
- Boys,no video games in school.- Who are you supposed to be?
- 孩子們 學校裡不准玩遊戲機 - 你哪位
- I'm the new cheerleading coach.- Do you bop?
- 我是新來的啦啦隊教練 - 你會跳舞嗎
Get to class,mates.
同學們 上課去
I've been trying to sound like Crocodile Dundee.Word of advice new Cheerios!Coach,Sue Sylvester.
我這是努力模仿鱷魚鄧迪的聲音
Try some pants.
還是穿褲子吧
Get to class!
上課去
That new cheerleading coach is one scary dude.
新啦啦隊教練是個狠角色
The moment I put that track suit on,the world bowed before me.I had one made in every color.
穿上運動服的那一刻 全世界都為我折服 我每種顏色都來了一套
Maybe it's time for a change,Coach.Everybody is scared of you now.It can't hurt to girl it up a bit.
教練 也許到變革的時候了 現在人人都怕你 女性化一點也未嘗不可
- You're early.- Geez!Oh,Brad!You scared the crap out of me!Warn me before you talk!
- 來得挺早呀 - 天哪 Brad 你嚇死我了 吱一聲會死嘛
I'm sorry,man.I'm having a bad week.
對不起 老兄 我這周過得不順
Tell me about it.I can't stop playing online blackjack.I owe thousands of dollars to some very sketchy people.
說來聽聽 我上網玩21點嚴重上癮 都欠別人好幾千塊了
Why doesn't anyone listen to me?I'm in 23 clubs!
為什麼沒人聽我的 我閱歷豐富
I probably would've been prom king if this school didn't have so many stoners.
這學校要是沒那麼多癮君子 我可能就已經是舞王了
And what's wrong with having a solid game plan?
認真地列個比賽計劃有什麼錯
- My house is getting foreclosed on.- And get this,my fianc called me a Puppet Master!
- 我家房子要被抵押了 - 還有 我的未婚夫叫我布偶大師
Well,if "pulling strings"  means that I encourage people to reach their fullest potential,
如果"提線"意味著 鼓勵他人釋放最大潛能
then,hell yeah,guilty as charged!
那好吧 我承認我有罪
Brad,if everyone just wants me to sit down and shut up...  that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
Brad 如果人人都想我老實坐好並閉嘴... 那我悉聽尊便
I'm gonna be right back here in the back corner.
那我就重新回到後排角落裡
- Believe me,that'll send a message...  - Blainey Days!
- 相信我 這就表示... - Blainey專場
- Blainey Days,wake up!We're sorry we didn't listen to you earlier.- Yeah,dawg.Our bad,yo!
- Blainey專場 醒醒 很抱歉之前沒聽你的 - 是的 老兄 我們的錯 喲
I'd love to say something really bitchy or even downright cruel,
我很想說一些極品的話 或者一些殘酷的大實話
but I can't,because you're clearly the most talented teenager at this school!
但我做不到 因為很顯然你是咱學校 最有才華的青年才俊
On this planet!
地球上也數一數二
Yeah,that's why we're best friends,even though  I'm straight and you're gay and I'm blond and you're gay.
是啊 所以我們是好哥們 即使我直你彎 即使我金你彎
- May the Force be with you.- Kids,I've got an awesome idea!
- 神力與你同在 - 孩子們 我有個絕妙的主意
This week's lesson is all about the most inspiring guy we know: Blaine!
這周我們上課的主題就是 這個最激勵人心的人物 Blaine
Ooh,child,Unique's got the blues!
親們 Unique有點心情低落
And the only way to cure 'em  is to hear Blaine's smooth-as-a-baby's-butt voice!
治癒的唯一良方就是 聽聽Blaine 那如同嬰兒屁屁般順滑的聲音
- Please,Blaine!- Please?
求你了 Blaine 求你了
Please?
求你了
- Yeah,Blaine!- Really?
- Blaine最棒 - 真的嗎
Well,if you guys insist.What should I sing?Oh,I know.Hit it!
如果你們執意要求的話 我該唱點啥呢 哦 知道了 走起
*Ooh,you make me live *Whatever this world can give to me *
Ooh you make me live Whatever this world can give to me
*It's you,you're all I see *  Ooh,you make me live now,honey *
It's you you're all I see Ooh you make me live now honey
*Ooh,you make me live *
Ooh you make me live
*Oh,you're the best friend that I ever had *
Oh you're the best friend that I ever had
*I've been with you such a long time *
I've been with you such a long time
*You're my sunshine,and I want you to know *
You're my sunshine and I want you to know
*That my feelings are true *I really love you  *Oh,you're my best friend.*
That my feelings are true I really love you Oh you're my best friend
*Ooh,you make me live!*
Ooh you make me live
*Ooh,I've been wandering around back to you *He'll come back to you *
Ooh I've been wandering around back to you He'll come back to you
*Rain or shine,you stood by me,girl *
Rain or shine you stood by me girl
*And I'm happy at home *  *You're my best friend *
And I'm happy at home You're my best friend
*Ooh,you make me live *Whenever this world is cruel to me *
Ooh you make me live Whenever this world is cruel to me
*I've got you to help me forgive *  *Ooh-ooh *
I've got you to help me forgive
*Ooh,you make me live now,honey *
Ooh you make me live now honey
*And I'm happy *  *You're my best friend *
And I'm happy You're my best friend
*Oh **Oh,you're my best friend *
Oh you're my best friend
*Ooh,you make me live,ooh-ooh *
Ooh you make me live ooh-ooh
*Ooh,you're my best friend *Oh-oh *Oh-oh!*
Ooh you're my best friend Oh-oh Oh-oh
*Oh-oh!You make me live!*
Oh-oh You make me live
Blainey Days,Blainey Days,what's wrong with you?
Blainey專場 Blainey專場 你鬧哪樣
Yeah,dude,you didn't say a word the entire class.Didn't even sing.
是啊 老兄 整節課你一言不發 連唱歌也不張嘴
You want us to call you a waaambulance?'Cause your pity party is out of control.
想讓我們幫你叫輛怨婦救護車嗎 因為你那可憐的聚會已經失控了
Yeah,girl,check yourself before you wreck yourself!
是呀 妹子 自我毀滅前先自省吧
And again.Five,six,seven,eight.Go one,two... four.Six,eight.
再來一次 五六七八 一二... 四六八
Sharper.Two,three,here it comes.Make sure we land.
更犀利一點 二三 來了哦 完全著地
Oh,God,okay,I've seen enough.Everyone stop.
天哪 好了 我瞭解了 都停下來
Look,I'm gonna do you guys a favor.
聽著 我幫你們個忙吧
You suck,and I can't be bothered to keep wasting my time.
你們太爛了 不能把我的寶貴時間浪費在你們身上
Hit the showers and get focused.Please,tomorrow,we are doing 540s.
去洗澡吧 集中精力 我們明天接著練
- Oh,my God,her,too?- All of them,actually.
- 天哪 她也滾了 - 老實說 跟所有人都滾過了
Jake,hey,uh,listen,I just wanted to say thanks  for sticking up for me in Glee Club.
Jake 聽著 我想對你說聲謝謝 你能在合唱團裡那麼力頂我
Sometimes I feel like I'm the only one  that cares about pushing us so we can nail it,you know?
有時我覺得好像只有我在推動大家 那樣我們才能成功 知道嗎
Yeah,I know,I mean,I'm getting pretty sick of it,too.
是啊 我知道 這些我也聽夠了
Um,I don't know how else to say this,but...  there's something's going on in the choir room.
我不知道如何開口 但是... 排練室裡有點不太對勁
I don't know if it's haunted or like a space-time rift happening,
我不知道是鬧鬼還是 發生了時空錯亂什麼的
but trust me,do yourself a favor,sit in the back corner.
但相信我 你自己感受下 坐後排角落那個位置
It's crazy.
太瘋狂了
Dance has never been our strong suit,but I think with Jake's help,we can really kick it up a notch.
舞蹈從來不是我們的強項 但我覺得有了Jake的幫忙
- Jake?- What's the point?
- Jake - 有啥意義嗎
I'm sorry?
你說什麼
Seriously,what is the point?I could choreograph a sick dance,none of you can keep up.
說真的 有啥意義嗎 我可以排個炫舞 但你們動作都跟不上
I mean,half of you can't even do it and won't even try.Why?
我是說 一半人都做不到 連試也不肯試 為什麼呢
Because you're not dancers.So let's not waste my time.
因為你們根本不是舞者 別浪費我的時間好嗎
Let's just do another cut-and-paste dance routine that even Tina can pick up.
我們還是跳那些不用動腦的機械動作吧 那些連Tina都能搞定的舞蹈
- You are such a conceited jerk.- I'm not conceited,I'm bored.
- 你真是個自以為是的混蛋啊 - 我不是自以為是 我受夠了
- Please,we've seen your dance moves.They're fine,not epic.- Oh,you want to see epic?
得了吧 我們見識過你的舞蹈動作 也就還好 到不了史詩般的程度
Give me a beat!
給哥個節奏
*Sittin' in the movie show thinking nasty thoughts *
Sittin' in the movie show thinking nasty thoughts
*Better be a gentleman or you'll turn me off,uh,huh *
Better be a gentleman or you'll turn me off
*That's right,and let me tell it *
That's right and let me tell it
*Nasty,nasty boys don't mean a thing,uh,huh *
Nasty nasty boys don't mean a thing
*Oh,you nasty boys *Nasty,nasty boys,don't ever change,huh *
Oh you nasty boys Nasty nasty boys don't ever change
*Oh,you nasty boys *I don't like no nasty girl *
I don't like no nasty girl
*I don't like nasty food,uh,huh *
I don't like nasty food
*Ooh,yeah *
Ooh yeah
*The only nasty thing I like is a nasty groove,uh!*
The only nasty thing I like is a nasty groove
*Will this one do?*
Will this one do
*Uh-huh,I know,sing *I'm not a prude,I just want some respect *
I know sing I'm not a prude I just want some respect
*That's right *So close the door if you want me to respond,ooh,yeah *
That's right So close the door if you want me to respond
*'Cause privacy is my middle name *
'Cause privacy is my middle name
*My last name is control *No,my first name ain't "baby" *
My last name is control No my first name ain't "baby"
*It's Janet... Ms.Jackson if you're nasty *
It's Janet... Ms.Jackson if you're nasty
*People of the world today *Are we looking for a better way of life?*
People of the world today Are we looking for a better way of life
*Say!We are a part of the rhythm nation *
Say We are a part of the rhythm nation
*Rhythm!*  *People of the world unite *
Rhythm People of the world unite
*Strength in numbers,we can get it right,one time *
Strength in numbers we can get it right one time
*Sing on *We are a part of the rhythm nation *
Sing on We are a part of the rhythm nation
*Everybody!*Nasty,nasty boys *  *Don't mean a thing *
Everybody Nasty nasty boys Don't mean a thing
*We are a part of the rhythm nation *Everybody sing it *
We are a part of the rhythm nation Everybody sing it
*Nasty,nasty boys don't ever change *
Nasty nasty boys don't ever change
*We are a part of the rhythm nation *
We are a part of the rhythm nation
*Rhythm... *We are a part of the rhythm nation *Sing it *
Rhythm... We are a part of the rhythm nation Sing it
*It goes to hear the rhythm *
It goes to hear the rhythm
*We are a part of the rhythm nation *  *Oh,you nasty boys.*
We are a part of the rhythm nation Oh you nasty boys
Baby-faced mocha-teen boy,arise!
娃娃臉咖啡男 快起來
Where is everyone?
人呢
They left minutes ago,muttering hateful comments  about your snide,
他們早走了 對你這個滿嘴謊言的痞子男
nasty mouth and bad boy attitudes.Now clear out!
邊走邊罵 老子要搞衛生了
Excuse me,Miss Alfano.
打擾一下 Alfano小姐
As much as I've really enjoyed learning about yarn these past three months,I was wondering,
過去三個月 我一直很享受上手工課 我想知道
since Arts and Crafts is my senior elective,if maybe I could do my own thing
既然工藝美術課是我高三的選修課 我是不是可以自己做點東西
and venture into felt  and fabric and even yarn and make a puppet?
嘗試用布和線自己縫製一個布偶
Your request surely begs the question,Why on earth would an 18-year-old man want to make a puppet?
你的請求引發了一個問題 究竟為什麼一個18歲男孩想要做布偶
Well... it's not just any puppet... It's a puppet of my fianc.
這可不是隨便一個布偶... 是給我未婚夫做的
We're 600 miles apart,and even though I get to see him tomorrow night,
我們遠隔600英里 即使我明晚就可以見到他
I'd really like to see him right now,even though it might be only in my imagination.
我現在就想見到他 即使存在我的幻想裡
Fine.Make a puppet.
好吧 做個布偶吧
- May I experiment with coupage?- No.
- 我能斗膽試一下嗎 - 不行
I forgave myself a long time ago.I think it's time I forgive you now.
我老早就原諒自己了 我覺得是時候該原諒你了
You are right.Please forgive me.
你說得對 求你原諒我吧
In this argument,I don't have a leg to stand on.
在這次爭論中 我沒法腳踏實地
Hey,Principal... uh,Coach.Um,geez,are you okay?
嘿 校長... 呃 教練 你沒事吧
Oh,what's with the shoes?Man,you have big feet.
這鞋子是什麼情況 你的腳夠大的
Well,I'm sorry if my femininity threatens you.
不好意思 如果我的女性氣質威脅到你
What is that?Did you just touch me with a puppet?
這什麼東西 你剛才用個布偶碰我了
Oh,I made it in Crafts class.
我在手工課上自己做的
- Get that thing out of here!I don't ever want to see that thing  in my hallway again!- What?
- 快把這玩意兒扔了 我不想再在走廊裡看見它 - 什麼
You can't just ban puppets.
你不能就這麼禁了人偶
Are you saying that because of the shoes?Are you less afraid of me?
是因為高跟鞋你才這麼說的嗎 你是沒那麼怕我了嗎
In a few days' time I am going to be evaluated  on my abilities to run this school.
再過幾天我就要接受治校能力評估了
If the school board comes here and sees schizophrenic students clearly off their meds talking to puppets,
如果校董事會過來 看到忘記吃藥的精分患者跟人偶說話
they are gonna think I don't have a handle on things.
他們會覺得我沒能力
- Well... Hey,hey!Kurt puppet!- This is contraband.
- 好吧... 喂 Kurt人偶啊 - 這是違禁品
And if I catch you with your hand  up the butt of anything that isn't human,you're in a world of trouble.
如果我再看到你手裡抓著別的東西 你就有大麻煩了
But... Be careful.
但是...小心一點兒
Damn it!
我去
Sue,I... look,I-I'm trying to work.
Sue 我...我這是在幹正事呢
Do you mind coming back in,like,an hour to barge in here  without knocking
你能不能一個小時後 再不敲門闖進來呢
and start insulting me for no reason?
然後無緣無故羞辱我
Oh,sure,sure,pal.I just,uh,I want to ask you a question first.
當然可以啦 哥們 我就是想問你個問題
Um... you're an oddly feminine man.
呃...你是一個氣質奇特的娘炮
- What?- Oh,please,you just literally did a pirouette.
- 什麼 - 得了吧 你剛剛還在單腳旋轉呢
Sue,just because a guy can dance doesn't make him effeminate.
Sue 就算一個男人會跳舞 也算不上是娘炮
That's what I'm saying.When you dance,somehow  you're able to maintain your manliness.
我就是這個意思 你跳舞時 還能保留一點男子氣概
Here's the thing:  Um... I happen to have a sizeable crush
是這樣的...我正好喜歡上了
on the handsomest man in the universe,Superintendent Bob Harris.
全宇宙最帥的男人 校董老大Bob Harris
I've had multiple conversations with him.
我跟他有過多次交流
In fact,several days ago,I was quite certain he was flirting with me.
事實上 幾天前 我確信他在跟我調情
But it turns out all this time he thought I was a man.
結果發現他一直以為我是男的
I blame the Johnny Cash song,"A Boy Named Sue.
這都是Johnny Cash那首歌鬧的 一個叫Sue的男孩
- You know what they used to say about Ginger Rogers?- No.
- 你知道他們以前是怎麼說Ginger Rogers的嗎 - 不知道
That she could lead her partner while dancing backwards in high heels.
她穿著高跟鞋倒退著跳舞時 還能領著她的舞伴
I have no idea how that is germane to this conversation.
這跟我們現在說的無關吧
Ginger Rogers was the pinnacle of femininity.
Ginger Rogers就是女性化的巔峰
I mean,she was one of the most famous dancers in the world,and her partner was Fred Astaire,
她是世界上最有名的舞蹈演員之一 她的舞伴則是Fred Astaire
maybe the greatest dancer of all time.
可能是有史以來最偉大的舞蹈家
Again,I don't know how this pertains to what I'm talking about.
我還是不覺得這跟我們的話題有關係
The point is,Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did...
關鍵在於 Fred Astaire做的事 Ginger Rogers也都做到了
only she did it backwards and in high heels.
只是她穿著高跟鞋倒著走
I mean,she managed to find a way to be feminine and strong.
她找到了既有力又不失女性風範的方法
Half the time when it looked like Fred Astaire was leading her?
有一半的時候 看起來像是Fred Astaire在領著她
- She was leading him.- Okay.
- 其實是她起主導作用 - 好吧
Tell you what.Let's make a dealI'll teach you to lead while dancing backwards in high heels,.
這麼著吧 我們做筆交易吧 我教你女性風範和強勢兼顧的方法
and you give me the $600 I need for new costumes at nationals.
你就給我全國賽買服裝的600美金
Nope.Forget it.
不行 得了吧
I'm sorry,there's no way in hell I'm going to give  the Glee Club more money for costumes
不好意思 讓我給合唱團 更多的錢買衣服 沒門兒
until you can explain to me how you paid for  that 18-cubic-foot inflatable Lady Gaga airbag
除非你給我解釋一下 你是怎麼整了那個巨大的充氣Lady Gaga氣囊
that you strapped onto the back  of the crippled kid's wheelchair.
就你繫在小瘸腿輪椅後面那個
- That was at least $1,000 right there,William.- Fine.Suit yourself.
- 光那玩意就花了將近1000美金 William - 好吧 那你隨意吧
Hey,doll.What do you say you and I cut a rug?
Hey,doll.What do you say you and I cut a rug?
*Heaven *I'm in heaven *And my heart beats so that I can hardly speak *
Heaven I'm in heaven And my heart beats so that I can hardly speak
*And I seem to find *The happiness I seek *When we're out together *
And I seem to find The happiness I seek When we're out together
*Dancing cheek to cheek *
Dancing cheek to cheek
*Heaven *I'm in heaven *And the cares that hung around me through the week *
Heaven I'm in heaven And the cares that hung around me through the week
*Seem to vanish *Like a gambler's lucky streak *
Seem to vanish Like a gambler's lucky streak
*When we're out together *  *Dancing cheek to cheek *
When we're out together  Dancing cheek to cheek
*Oh,I love to climb a mountain *
Oh,I love to climb a mountain
*And to reach the highest peak *
And to reach the highest peak
*But it doesn't thrill me half as much *
But it doesn't thrill me half as much
*As dancing cheek to cheek *
As dancing cheek to cheek
*Oh,I love to go out fishing *  *Go out fishing*
Oh,I love to go out fishing   Go out fishing
*In a river or a creek *  *Or a creek*
In a river or a creek Or a creek
*But I don't enjoy it half as much *
But I don't enjoy it half as much
*As dancing cheek to cheek *
As dancing cheek to cheek
*And I seem to find *The happiness I seek *When we're out together *
And I seem to find The happiness I seek When we're out together
*Dancing cheek to cheek.*
Dancing cheek to cheek.
Come on,Coach!Wake up!I've got to shop for a mini-fridge for college!
快點 教練 起床 我得去買大學要用的迷你冰箱
Oh,God,let it go.I don't want a girlfriend.
天吶 放開我 我不想要什麼女朋友
Shut up.I don't want to be your girlfriend,either.
閉嘴 我也不想做你女朋友
Then what?I'm late for class.
那是怎麼了啊 我上課要遲到了
I'm pregnant.With your baby.
我懷了 你的孩子
- Bree,this is... - All I'm going to ask is that  you come with me to the doctor,okay?
- Bree 這... - 我只想讓你陪我去醫生那裡 行嗎
- Wh-What are your parents going to say?- No... parents.
- 你父母怎麼說啊 - 跟父母沒關係
This is staying between us.Forever.It's the right thing to do.Right?
就我們倆知道 永遠都得這樣 這麼做是對的 是嗎
Well,well,well.If it isn't Miss Sally Field in Not Without My Puppet.
喲 這不是沒了人偶的Sally Field嘛
Did you really think I was too stupid to suspect  that you would come back here
你以為我傻啊 你以為我不會懷疑你會回來嗎
under the cloak of darkness  to claim your monstrous puppet-bride,you strange,tiny,doe-eyed pervert?
趁著夜黑風高 來拿你那只奇醜無比的新郎人偶 你這個怪胎 矮子 鹿眼變態
Kindly remove your fist from Puppet Hummel's butt  and place him gingerly on the desk.
把你的手從Hummel人偶的屁股上挪開 把它小心放在桌上
And now report to detention for the rest of the week.
這周剩下來幾天放學後都要留校
But I was supposed to fly to New York to see Kurt's first big show.
可是我要飛到紐約 去看Kurt的第一場大演出啊
Well,then you're gonna have to cancel Wonder Woman's invisible jet,
不好意思了 你最好去退機票
or whatever magic discount  bullet train you kids use for your weekly jaunts to New York.
或者是你們每週去紐約買的打折高鐵票
Now,get out of here.Go feel shame.
現在 滾出去 感受一下羞愧
Hi.
嗨
Hey.Did you get your ticket that I reserved for you,house-left?
你拿到我給你留的票了嗎 在戲院左邊
Kurt,I was gonna call you.Um,please don't be mad,but... I'm not in New York,I'm in Lima.
Kurt 我正要打給你呢 別生氣啊 但是 我沒在紐約 我在利馬
A-Are you kidding?What happened?Did you miss your flight?
你開玩笑吧 怎麼回事啊 你是誤機了嗎
- A-Are you okay?- I-I'm fine.I'm just,um...  I'm just trying to explain.
- 你沒事吧 - 我 我沒事 我正要解釋呢
Yes,why don't you explain... and it better be a good explanation.
好啊 你解釋啊...好好給我解釋一下
Well,Principal Sylvester gave me detention,and she said if I tried to skip it
Sylvester校長給了我留校處分 她還說如果我想偷溜
that she was gonna suspend me  and put it on my permanent record.
她就會讓我停學 然後記到我檔案裡
Hang on.Whoa,whoa,wait one second.And you weren't going to call me?
等會兒 喂喂 等會兒 而且你還沒打算打給我是嗎
I-I was trying my best not to hurt you.
我盡力了 不想傷害你
All I did was steal back the Kurt puppet that I made in crafts class.
我只不過是想把在手工課上 做的Kurt人偶偷回來
Excuse me?The-the what puppet?What the hell are you talking about?
什麼 什麼人偶 你到底在說什麼啊
Uh,I-I know,it's,uh,it's kind of... a weird story.But basically,I was missing you.
我知道 這說起來有點...奇怪 但是 我就是想你了
And is that how you see me?
你就是那樣看我的嗎
As a thing of felt and cloth and button eyes that has no feelings,
一身毛氈和布 扣子眼睛 沒感情的東西嗎
that you can play with and manipulate and then discard whenever you're bored?
你能操控的玩物 然後無聊了就把我扔了
- Oh,no. - I'm a person,Blaine.
- 不是的 - 我是個人 Blaine
I am flesh and blood and bone,and this is a really big night for me,and I needed you to be here.
我有血有肉有骨頭 今晚對我真的很重要 我需要你的陪伴
Kurt...
Kurt...
- Hey.- We can release Blaine's seat.
- 喂 - 我們可以把Blaine的座位放出去了
I don't think that's gonna be necessary.
我看是沒這個必要了
One person?
只有一個人嗎
- And he thinks Angela Lansbury's performing.- I told you so.
- 而且他以為是Angela Lansbury要演出 - 我說了吧
Let's be real for a second.
我們還是現實一點吧
I've never been all that nice to you,and I don't  really get whatever's... going on with you,
我一直都對你挺差的 我也不知道你這...是怎麼回事
but I have to say,there's a part of me that really admires it.
不過我得說 我還是有一點欣賞你的
When a woman of my stature needs a makeover,she rings up all her best gays,
像我這麼大個的女人要化妝時 她都會打給她最要好的Gay蜜
but unfortunately,Porcelain,the Sassy Toothless Elf,is in New York.
很不幸的是 瓷娃娃 那個很潮的沒長牙的小精靈 在紐約
So... God's most fabulous mistake,I turn to you.
所以呢...上帝最美妙的錯誤啊 我需要你的幫助
I want to look more like a lady.
我想打扮得更像個女人
Girl,I have already pulled out my makeup kit... I got you,boo.
姐們 我帶了我的化妝箱... 我可以幫你
Welcome,teen delinquents,to detention,AKA "The Beck-fast Club,"
歡迎各位問題青少年來留校 也叫做The Beck-fast Club
named after Miss Becky Jackson,who has been here more than any other student.
是以Becky Jackson小姐命名的 她在這兒呆的時間比誰都長
- Yeah,why is that?- 'Cause I like saying bad words,bitch!
- 是嗎 為什麼啊 - 因為我喜歡爆粗口 婊子
Jacob X.Puckerman,you were caught red-handed starting another  exciting
Jacob X.Puckerman 你在William McKinley高中走廊上打架
yet forbidden fistfight in the William McKinley High School hallways.
被抓了個正著 架打得漂亮但那是不允許的
Why are you such a mysterious musical bad boy?
你怎麼是個如此神秘的音樂男孩呢
It is now 4:01.You have exactly eight hours to ponder the horrific  error of your pubescent ways.
現在是4:01 你還有八個小時的時間 來反省你青春期犯下的嚴重錯誤
- There will be no talking and no monkeyshines,is that clear?- Crystal.
- 不能說話也不能胡鬧 明白嗎 - 明白
You know,maybe we could use this time  to get to know each other a little better.
我們應該利用這段時間 好好瞭解對方
We could sit in a circle on the floor and tell each other  about our core wounds.
我們可以在地上圍成一圈坐著 說一說各自最大的創傷
Or you shut your hole.I'm going to college soon,I don't have time for your lame-ass bull crap.
你閉嘴吧 我就要去上大學了 我可沒時間聽你廢話
I'm sorry,Blaine Warbler.But that was totally inappropriate.Please come sit with me.
抱歉 Blaine Warbler 那真是太失禮了 跟我坐一塊吧
Sometimes I fly off the handle.Like yesterday,when I taped Dottie's buns together.
我有時會發脾氣 就像昨天 我把Dottie的頭髮粘在一起了
I did it for my old man.I wanted him to think I was cool.
我是做給我爸看的 想讓他覺得我很酷
That's really heavy,Becky.Thanks for sharing.What's going on with you,Blaine?
那真是太沉重了 Becky 謝謝分享 你又怎麼回事了啊 Blaine
Well,to tell the truth,guys,I feel really,really guilty about  missing Kurt's show in New York.
說真的 各位 錯過Kurt在紐約的演出 我十分內疚
Why?It's a stupid cover band.
這有什麼 只是個蠢爆了的翻唱樂隊啊
- And,dude,you go to New York all the time... you were just there last week.- True.But Kurt needs me.
- 而且 哥們 你總是去紐約啊...上周就去了 - 沒錯 但是Kurt需要我
- We all need you,because you are so awesome.- Yeah,you're America's gay sweetheart.
- 我們都需要你啊 因為你很棒 - 沒錯 你是美國基佬甜心
Thanks,guys.You guys are,like,my only real friends.
謝謝你們 你們就好像是 我僅有的真正的朋友
- But we're not real; we're puppets.- Maybe that's a bad thing.
- 但我們不是真的呀 我們是人偶 - 或許這是壞事
Maybe the fact that I can only really feel like myself  with friends
或許我只在跟我能控制的朋友相處時
I can totally control is keeping me  from really feeling like I'm close to anyone.
才能感覺到真實的自我 妨礙我去真正親近別人
Maybe it's indicative of a deeper intimacy issue.
或許這意味著密切關係恐懼症
Or maybe everyone should just wise up  and start doing everything you see,
或許大家應該放聰明點 就按你想的做
because you are so right on all the time.
因為你一直都是對的
By the way,did you notice you're  now having puppet fantasies outside the choir room?
對了 你有沒有發現啊 你現在在排練室外也有人偶幻想了
That's not normal.Seriously,you might want to get a CAT scan.
那可不正常 說真的 你最好做個腦部掃瞄
Hello,hello.Wake up.Hey.
嘿 醒醒 醒醒
Will you cover for me,please?I've got to leave early.
幫我掩護下 我得早退
- Uh,y-yeah,sure.Why?- It's not important.Later.
- 呃 行啊 你要去哪 - 小事 晚點再說
Hey,so,are you ready to go?
可以走了不
No need.The crimson tide is rolling again.
不必 紅色浪潮來襲
I got my period.I'm not pregnant.I guess I was just late... this month.
我大姨媽來了 沒懷孕 可能這個月有點遲
Are you serious?That's awesome news.Oh,I am so relieved.
真的假的 太好了 我解脫了
You're relieved?Why?I was the one who had to go to the doctor visit.
解脫 為什麼 要去看醫生的是我
No,I just mean that I'm relieved that the whole thing  is over,you know,for the both of us.
我解脫是因為一切都結束了 對我們倆來說都是好事
Let me hit you with the blunt instrument of reality,Puckerman.
別被殘酷的現實嚇尿 Puckerman
You're still you,a douchey playboy who's gonna spend the rest of his life
你還是你 娘炮花花公子
dealing with one mess after another as long as he lives.
這輩子就是不停地處理一攤又一攤濫情
One of these days,you are gonna knock someone up,
總有一天 你會把人肚子搞大
and I feel bad  for whoever has to have a child that shares your DNA.
誰的娃要是繼承了你的DNA 真為她不值
Hey,I'm gonna make a great father one day.
我會成為一個好父親的
To who?Your seven kids by seven different women?Not unless you change.
媽媽是誰 七個孩子七個媽 不可能 除非你改變
Bree,look,I'm sorry,okay?I know this whole thing was really scary and traumatic...
Bree 聽著 對不起 我知道這一切對你很傷
Just do me a favor and stay away from me from now on.You're toxic.
請你現在離我遠點行嗎 受不了
Little known fact?
沒人知道
McKinley saved a bundle on new lockers by using recycled metal.
麥金利利用回收金屬節省了儲物櫃的費用
These lockers are actually Kalashnikovs  that were melted down during the war in Chechnya.
這些儲物櫃的材料 是由車臣戰爭的衝鋒鎗溶解後製成
- Uh,Principal Sylvester,- Yes.
- Sylvester校長 - 怎麼
I owe you an apology.
我欠你一個道歉
I...  I get in "business mode," and I may not be that observant,
我之前沉浸在"工作模式"所以有點沒看清
so I... Well,I...  might've overlooked your more... feminine side.
似乎忽視了你女人的一面
No worries,Superintendant.No worries.Please.
不用擔心 主任 不用擔心
And this... is the choir room of McKinley's pride and joy,our national championship glee club,the New Directions.
這裡就是麥金利引以為傲的合唱室 這是我們的全國冠軍歡樂合唱團 新方向
Attention,McKinley School Board,Sue Sylvester has put our children  in grave danger.
小心 麥金利校董們 Sue Sylvester讓我們的孩子陷入危險之中
There is a gas leak in this room  that is a direct result of Sue Sylvester's failed leadership!
這個房間氣體洩漏 全由Sue Sylvester失敗的領導所致
No,there was a gas leak in this room,but I fixed it.
不 這兒確實有過氣體洩漏 但我已經修好了
I know a gas-induced fantasy dance sequence  when I experience one.
我有一次吸入氣體導致幻想舞蹈場面
And despite the fact that facilities management is under your jurisdiction,Janitor Figgins,
且不說設備管理是您的工作範圍 Figgins
I found the problem,I corrected it  and now I'm cutting your pay in half.
我發現問題 及時改正 現在我要把你的收入減半
Principal Sylvester,we've seen enough.
Sylvester校長 我們看得差不多了
Yours is precisely the type of leadership this school needs.
您確實就是這所學校所需要的領導類型
The board would like to make you principal on a permanent basis.
校董會會任命您為終身校長
- Congratulations,Sue.- Oh,thank you so much,Superintendant.
- 恭喜 Sue - 謝謝 主任
- How about we go out and celebrate?- Excuse me?
- 不如我們去慶祝一下 - 什麼
- Would you like to go out on a date with me?- Um... no.I don't want to do that.
- 你願意和我約會嗎 - 不 沒有啊
Am I okay?I mean,is this what it feels like to be losing your mind?
我沒事吧 這就是失心瘋的感覺嗎
I'm unraveling.I feel like Mel Gibson in The Beaver.
我快分裂了 像是裡的Mel Gibson
More like Mel Gibson in Mad Max,with your abs and your... leather.
更像裡的他 你有腹肌 還有...皮
Wait,what leather?
等等 什麼皮
The leather I was imagining you in  when I was rubbing vapor cream all over your smooth... hairless... chest.
是我幻想在你光滑的胸口上抹蒸汽奶油的情景
Tina,I'm engaged.
Tina 我已經訂婚了
- Hey,what's going on?- Uh... nothing.
- 嘿 什麼情況 - 沒什麼
I'm-I'm just,um,cleaning my head out.Just trying to figure some stuff out.
我在清空思緒 想些事情
- Is that supposed to be me?- What?!That's... that-that's crazy.
- 那是我嗎 - 什麼 怎麼可能 你瘋了啊
- She has Asian eyes and my exact dress.- Total coincidence.
- 她由亞洲人的眼睛 和我穿一樣的裙子 - 巧合罷了
Not everything is about you,Tina.What do you want?
不是什麼事都和你有關係 Tina 你想怎樣
I just wanted to let you know that everybody feels bad.
我只想讓你知道 大家都不太好
We spent pretty much the whole Glee session discussing how much pressure
幾乎整場歡樂合唱團會議都在討論
- you're under with nationals,graduation... - The engagement.
- 全國賽 畢業對你的壓力 - 還有訂婚吧
You were just trying to exert some control.And the truth is,you should have some.You've earned it.
你一直試圖掌控 確實應當如此 這是你應得的
Sam suggested you should have the lead on one of the songs at nationals.
Sam提議讓你在全國賽上領唱一首歌
So we took a vote and it was unanimous.Piano,a capella,whatever you think is right.
我們全票通過 鋼琴 清唱 全聽你的
- Thanks,Tina.- Of course.
- 謝謝 Tina - 客氣
So if you're done being a puppet master,do you think you could take your hand out from under my dress?
玩偶大師這件事你玩夠了吧 那能不能請你別再把手伸到我的裙子裡
- Um... - Yeah.- Um... - It's okay.
- 呃 好 - 沒事
- Sorry about that.- Thanks.
- 抱歉 - 謝謝
- I'm gonna miss having a Kurt puppet though.He did anything I said.- Anything?
- 我還是很懷念擁有一個Kurt娃娃 我說什麼他都照做 - 什麼都照做
- All right,settle down,Puppet Tina.Okay.I get it.- Blainey Days...
- 行了 Tina娃娃 我知道了 - Blaine的節日
Marley.Marley,Marley,please.Please just listen.Please.
Marley Marley Marley 求求你先聽我說
30 seconds.Go.
就30秒 開始
I miss you.Every minute of every day.
我很想你 分分秒秒都是
And I know that I screwed things up really badly,and I'm sorry.
我知道我太爛了 對不起
I know what I lost and I know that I can't be without you.I need you.
我知道我自己失去了什麼 我不能沒有你 我需要你
I don't want to be this jerk anymore,and you are the only one who can make me a better person.
我不希望一直這樣混蛋下去 你是唯一能讓我變好的那個人
- A good person.- I'm not here to fix you,Jake.
- 讓我成為一個好人 - 我不是來糾正你的 Jake
I know,I know,I know.That's why I'm here.
我知道 所以我才過來
To make it right,to make it better,to make me better.
想辦法變好 讓我變好
I'm sorry,but we gave it a try and it... just wasn't right.
抱歉 但我們試過了 可是沒用
So after all that... you're saying you don't have any feelings for me?
發生了這麼多事 你是說你對我沒感覺了嗎
- I think that you're a good friend and teammate... -  Marley...
- 我把你當成好朋友 好隊友 - Marley...
- but I just don't feel the same as you.Not anymore.- Marley,please.
- 我和你的感覺不一樣 也不會再有那樣的感覺 - Marley 求你了
I got to get to class.I'll see you later in Glee Club.
我該去上課了 之後在歡樂合唱團見
Look,I know we don't know why Kurt called this meeting.
對 我們還不知道為什麼Kurt要開會
It's probably to retire the band,but we can't rub it in and say,"I told you so."
可能是解散樂隊 但我們不能不同嘀咕"早說了吧"
That would be devastating.
太傷人了
Well,I wouldn't do that,and I'm not gonna let Kurt disband Pamela Lansbury.
我不會這麼做 我也不會讓Kurt解散Pamela Lansbury樂隊
Look,I might not agree with all of his decisions,but he is our leader
我並不贊同他的所有決定 但他是我們的隊長
and he's an artist,and artists should be allowed to fail.
而且他是個藝術家 應該容忍藝術家的失敗
- Who says we failed?Cronuts,anyone?- Hi.
- 誰說我們失敗了 可頌圈 有人要嗎 - 嗨
Oh,this?No big deal.
這沒什麼大不了的
Just a little token from the booking agency of the Williamsburg Music Hall,
威廉斯堡音樂廳售票處給予的特權
which is the location of our second gig!
我們要在那兒進行我們的第二次演出
- What?Are you serious?- How?
- 什麼 真的假的 - 怎麼做到的
Okay,true,we only had one audience member at our last show,
沒錯 上一場演出我們只有一個觀眾
but it happened to be the right audience member because,not only was he a devoted Angela Lansbury fan,
但卻是再合適不過的觀眾 他不僅是Angela Lansbury的死忠飯
but he also liked what he saw,made a secret bootleg  and passed it along to his nephew,
他也很喜歡他所看到的東西 偷偷走私了送給他的外甥
- who works at the Williamsburg Music Hall.- The Williamsburg Music Hall,which also just happens to be...
- 而他外甥恰好在威廉斯堡音樂廳工作 - 威廉斯堡音樂廳又恰好是...
- One of the hottest venues in Brooklyn.Good work,fearless leader.- Well,it wasn't just me.
- 布魯克林最熱門的場館之一 好樣的 勇敢的隊長- 不只是因為我
It was... also a lot of luck and-and you guys.
一部分也源於運氣 還有你們
Because,you know,whether Pamela Lansbury implodes or explodes,
因為無論Pamela Lansbury是否堅持下去
I really have to thank you guys for sticking by me.
我真的很感謝你們能夠緊緊跟隨我
- Uh,package for Kurt Hummel.- Okay.
- Kurt Hummel的包裹 - 好
- Thank you.- Thank you.
- 謝謝
Oh,it's from Blaine.He sends a gift to say sorry for missing the performance the other night.
是Blaine的 他送了我一個禮物 以表未出席那晚表演的歉意
That's so nice!
太好了
Okay,that is creepy as hell.Is there one for each of us?
- 太TM嚇人了 - 一人一個嗎
Guys,I just wanted to apologize to all of you.
各位 非常抱歉
I've been a little bit controlling lately and it's not cool.
我這陣子控制感太強 這樣很不好
I've made some changes though and I've learned that sometimes  you just need to let go.
我已經有所改變 我也明白有時候要學會放下
- Cut the strings,so to speak.- I bet you'll still be bossy as hell.
- 也可以說是 脫離掌控 - 我打賭你還是那個專橫
Actually,I hope to be more of a leader,as opposed to being just bossy,Kitty.
事實上 我更希望成為一個領導者 而不是專橫 Kitty
So to celebrate this new laissez-faire Blaine,I've made some felt peace offerings.
為一個全新的放任主義的Blaine而歡呼吧 我準備了一些贈品
Voila.
哇哦
- It has glasses!- I think we look alike.
還有眼鏡 真像
*Dog goes woof *Cat goes meow *Bird goes tweet *And mouse goes squeak *
Dog goes woof Cat goes meow Bird goes tweet And mouse goes squeak
*Cow goes moo *Frog goes croak *And the elephant goes toot *Ducks say quack *
Cow goes moo Frog goes croak And the elephant goes toot Ducks say quack
*And fish go blub *And the seal goes ow ow ow *But there's one sound *
And fish go blub And the seal goes ow ow ow But there's one sound
*That no one knows *  *What does the fox say?*
That no one knows   What does the fox say?
*Ding,ding,ding,ding,ding-ding-ding *
Ding,ding,ding,ding,ding-ding-ding
*What the fox say?*
What the fox say?
*Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow *  *Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow *Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow *
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow  Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pow
*Hee,hee,hee *A-hee,hee,hee *  *A-hee,hee,hee *What the fox say?*
Hee,hee,hee A-hee,hee,hee A-hee,hee,hee What the fox say?
*Ooh... *Ooh... *  *What does the fox say?
Ooh... Ooh...   What does the fox say?
*The secret of the fox *Ancient mystery *Somewhere deep in the woods *
The secret of the fox Ancient mystery Somewhere deep in the woods
*I know you're hiding *  *What is your sound?*
I know you're hiding What is your sound?
*Will we ever know?*
Will we ever know?
*Will always be a mystery *  *What do you say?*
Will always be a mystery What do you say?
*You're my guardian angel *Hiding in the woods *What is your sound?*
You're my guardian angel Hiding in the woods What is your sound?
*Wa-wa-way-do *Wub-wid-bid-dum-way-do*Wa-wa-way-do*
Wa-wa-way-do Wub-wid-bid-dum-way-doWa-wa-way-do
*Will we ever know?*
Will we ever know?
*I want to *Wa-wa-way-do *
I want to Wa-wa-way-do
*Know,I want to know *I want to know *Wa-wa-way-do.*
Know,I want to know I want to know Wa-wa-way-do.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-------------------------- 本論壇字幕僅翻譯交流學習之用 禁止任何商業用途否則後果自負 --------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-橙子
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: 南極洲洲長 風聲 Solitary 琥珀時間 校對: Andrea∞Quinn 時間軸:YTET-橙子
Glee Season5Episode 7
歡樂合唱團 第五季 第七集 完